<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://nullsender.github.io/thoughts/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 23:32:01 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://nullsender.github.io/thoughts/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>https://nullsender.github.io/thoughts/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 23:32:01 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nullsender.github.io/thoughts/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;my-greeting&#34;&gt;My greeting&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the zero people reading this I bid you welcome. This is my humble attempt at making a small blog.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have now used my entire evening setting up a workflow such that I can easily write a blogpost. I am currently using Hugo and I am writing this text with GNU nano 8.2.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My intentions for doing this is that I sometimes get interrested in things, think about them, read about them, and sudenly no more. The thoughts stop and when I think back it feels&#xA;like something important has been erased. It is kind of strange, we get all these thoughts and the next moment they are gone. A lot of the thoughts I have had where unproductive and&#xA;not worth reproducing or remembering. Maybe only the thoughts and actions worth remembering are remembered. Anyways I have for a long time wanted to create a space where I can write&#xA;some of these thoughts down and here we are. Another thing is that I want to become a better writer and thinker and I do belive writing a lot will help me in this pursuit.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
